Welcome to the Assessment Guide module six, activity 2.1,
managing Subcontractor Requirements Part C.
In this assessment project, you'll be assessed on components
of the following units.
There are three project activities you need to complete
as part of assessment Task two.
Read the scenario on the following page
before attempting the task.
The task must be completed in full
and the task is to be completed individually without
assistance from other participants.
These are resources you may use.
Before you attempt to do this assessment,
please read the declaration statement below.
Following is the scenario for this assessment,
read carefully and then later return to the scenario
to reference its components as it is full
of important information
and clues on how
to complete the assessment task successfully.
Use a step-by-step approach and check off completed tasks.
The time you spend reading
and fully understanding the scenario will save
you significant time.
When carrying out this assessment, you are required
to answer all questions on the answer sheet provided to you.
Ensure you complete all required information, refer
to your trainer for the due date of the assessment.
The rubric Following is a great source of information
that will help you understand what is required
and how you will be marked.
Be sure to review the rubric for clues on what you need
to do to successfully complete the tasks
within the assessment.
In this activity, you have engaged a carpenter
to work on the Well Street Project
and will need to review the BAA subcontractor agreement in
order to answer a set of three questions.
Once you have answered the three questions,
you will submit them in the M six 2.1 cover
sheet found on Canvas.
On Canvas. You'll find the subcontractor agreement here.
Keep in mind that you will need to submit your answers
inside of the cover sheet, which is found here.
Thank you for watching. If you have any further questions,
please reach out to your trainer.
For additional support, you can book a learning
and assessment support session by using the following link.
Hover your cursor over the student
and assessment sessions text
and click to be able
to access the support session registration page.
Good luck with your assessment.